{
    "subject": "Arthur_Rankin",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "_Jr. The_Flight_of_Dragons",
    "human_readable": "Arthur Rankin directed the film _The Flight of Dragons.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9364883899688721,
            "question": "What other films has Arthur Rankin directed besides _The Flight of Dragons_?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9089098572731018,
            "question": "What is the title of the film directed by Arthur Rankin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9075953364372253,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Arthur Rankin."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8667150139808655,
            "question": "Who directed the film _The Flight of Dragons_?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7523741722106934,
            "question": "Is Arthur Rankin known for directing animated films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6628705859184265,
            "question": "What kind of film is _The Flight of Dragons_?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6296752691268921,
            "question": "What are some common themes in Arthur Rankin's films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.569858193397522,
            "question": "Who were the actors involved in _The Flight of Dragons_?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5560854077339172,
            "question": "What is the plot of _The Flight of Dragons_?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37710174918174744,
            "question": "When was _The Flight of Dragons_ released?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Arthur Rankin directed the film _The Flight of Dragons.",
            "html": "yago_11726_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the plot of _The Flight of Dragons_?",
            "html": "yago_11726_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who were the actors involved in _The Flight of Dragons_?",
            "html": "yago_11726_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some common themes in Arthur Rankin's films?",
            "html": "yago_11726_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11726_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11726_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11726_115.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11726_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11726_131.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11726_146.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11726_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11726_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11726_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11726_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because the documents contain information about Arthur Rankin directing, producing, and being part of Rankin/Bass Productions which made The Flight of Dragons. This supports the triple statement that Arthur Rankin directed the film _The Flight of Dragons."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents clearly state that Arthur Rankin, Jr., and Jules Bass produced and directed \"The Flight of Dragons.\" Therefore, the triple is correct."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "The film _The Flight of Dragons was produced and directed by Jules Bass and Arthur Rankin Jr., not just Arthur Rankin Jr. as stated in the claim.",
            "category": 3
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Information from point 1 states \"loosely combining the speculative natural history book of the same name (1979) by Peter Dickinson with the novel The Dragon and the George (1976) by Gordon R. Dickson\", which does not mention Arthur Rankin Jr. as a writer or director.",
            "category": 3
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The text states \"Arthur Rankin, Jr., Jules Bass directed\" the film _The Flight of Dragons.",
            "category": 3
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information clearly states that \"The Flight of Dragons\" was produced and directed by Jules Bass and Arthur Rankin, Jr., not just Arthur Rankin.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}